

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, ASP. Net MVC, Net Core, Web API, C#, HTML, CSS, MySQL, SQLite, JIRA, GitHub, TestRail



Current Designation: Software Developer -Dot Net Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: Mphasis Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Telecommunication]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project

Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, ASP . Net MVC, . Net Core, Web

API,C#,HTML,CSS,MySQL,SQLite,JIRA,GitHub,TestRail

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

I am a software developer with 2 years of experience looking for challenging role which demands the best of my professional ability in terms of, technical, analytical and management skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the IT sector.

Work Experience

Mphasis as Software Developer -Dot Net

Oct 2018 to Till Date

Developed and implemented software solutions based on client requirements in ASP .Net Application

Optimized the code and query to increase the performance of application

Worked in Frontend side and got an exposure to Reactis, Able to understand and debug frontend language

HP- Firmware Security API | May 2019 to Present

Developed and implemented software solutions based on client requirements in .Net core

Implemented Webhook, logging concepts

Software Tester

HP- Firmware Security Tool | Jan 2019 to April 2019

Create Test cases and manually testing the Web application Create and run SQL queries for Data validation in database Had scope to manage test cases in TestRail

MLA Trainee | Oct 2018 to Dec 2018

Undergone 2months of .Net MVC training in Mphasis Learning Academy

Had a chance to work on 1 individual & 1 group project

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Telecommunication) from K.S. INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, BANGALORE in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C#, HTML/CSS			
Asp .NEt MVC			0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
.net core, Web API			
MySQL, SQLite			
Design Patterns			
JIRA			
GitHub			
TestRail			
VISUAL STUDIO			
Postman, Fiddler			
SQLITE			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Kannada				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time